world-newspapers.com 2005-03-07

# World-Newspapers.com Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

World-Newspapers.com is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information which you provide online.

 **Personal Information**

We do not ask for registration on the site, nor do we keep track of any personal information (name, address, e-mail address) of any visitors to the site.

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad or specific requests for information about our site.

We will not disclose any personal information to any third party for any reason. We will never send you any advertisements or unsolicited information about the site.

 **Traffic data**

Each time a visitor comes to World-Newspapers.com site, our servers - like most on the Web - collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor's domain name, referral data, and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform).

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our site (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the site, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

 **Advertising**

World-Newspapers.com works with several companies to deliver ads to the site. Our agreement with such companies specifies that information about our users may only be used to deliver ads on our site. We do not provide any personal information, such as names, postal addresses, phone numbers, or e-mail addresses, to ad companies.

As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
<http://www.usubscribe.com/privacy.cfm>  
<http://cj.com/privacy.asp>  

**Use of cookies**

A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used for several purposes, but we only use cookies in a limited way. We allow our traffic counter to use cookies to identify the number of unique browsers that visit our sites and to keep track of how many times browsers visit the site.

We can also allow ad companies to use cookies to help serve advertisments. They are just used to help serve ads on the site you are visiting. Cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines, so advertisers will not know who you are. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.

 **Disclaimer**

We cannot be responsible for the content of sites that world-newspapers.com links to. If inappropropriate content is added to the site after we have linked to the site please contact us and inform about the linked site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact:

Marius Kazokaitis  
tel.: (370) 2 703660  
Our postal address is  
Lithuania, Pasilaiciu 6-86  
Vilnius, LT-2000
